Be Afraid is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Drew Gabreski.
Not long after John Chambers and his family arrive at their new home in a small
country town of Pennsylvania, John begins to experience sleep paralysis.
Lying there paralyzed, trapped within his own
nightmare, other-worldly beings visit John.
They are entities which exist in the darkest shadows of the night
and can only be seen out of the corner of one's eye.
These encounters begin to haunt John, transforming to complete
terror as he discovers the entities' sole purpose...
the abduction of his seven year old son.
In the end, John will uncover the town's horrific secret, a portal on his land, and make one last
attempt to save his son before the shadow people permanently take him away to their world.
Dr. John Chambers, played by Brian Krause.
Heather Chambers, played by Jaimi Paige.
Chief Collins, played by Louis Herthum.
Ben Chambers, played by Jared Abrahamson.
Christine Booth, played by Michelle Hurd.
Nathan Chambers, played by Michael Leone.
Beau Is Afraid is a 2023 American epic surrealist tragicomedy horror
film written, directed, and co-produced by Ari Aster.
The film stars Joaquin Phoenix as the title character, and also includes a supporting cast consisting of Patti LuPone, Nathan Lane, Amy Ryan, Kylie
Rogers, Parker Posey, Stephen McKinley Henderson, Hayley Squires, Michael Gandolfini, Zoe Lister-Jones, Armen Nahapetian, and Richard Kind.
Its plot follows the mild-mannered but paranoia-ridden Beau as he embarks on a surreal odyssey
to get home to his mother's house, realizing his greatest fears along the way.
Distributed by A24, Beau Is Afraid premiered at the Alamo Drafthouse Cinema on April 1, 2023, and began a limited
theatrical release in the United States on April 14, 2023, before a wide release the following week.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics but was a box-office bomb,
grossing $12 million against a net production cost of $35 million.
Phoenix received a Golden Globe nomination for his performance.
The film explores themes of suicide, pennsylvania, usa,
loss of loved one, murder, shadowy figures.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.